I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor
A bitch constrictor
When I met her I didn’t know she got hooks
Accompanied by her spicy looks
Feminine wiles for both my heads
Destruction and terror in her stead
She twirl me around like a tortellini
Got me thinkin’ with my coney island weenie
My brain feels like a tetrazzini
It’s no fair you big meanie
Before I know it – she’s up to my foot
Before I know it – she’s up to my leg
Before I know it – she’s up to my knee
Before I know it – she up to my
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor
A bitch constrictor
Before I know it – she’s up to my waist
Before I know it – she’s up to my belly
Before I know it – she’s up to my ribs
Before I know it – she up to my chest
I gotta get loose before it’s too late
Sealed and delivered is my fate
Can’t get rid of her like something that
I ate
Please god let me emancipate
The light is fading from my face
Perfume burns my eyes like mace
Titties was the cause of my fall from grace
I get trapped up in that special place
Before I know it – she’s up
to my neck
Before I know it – she’s up to my face
Before I know it – I’m over my head
Before I know it – she up to my
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor
A bitch constrictor
When I met her I didn’t know she got hooks
Accompanied by her spicy looks
Feminine wiles for both my heads
Destruction and terror in her stead
She twirl me around like a tortellini
Got me thinkin’ with my coney island weenie
My brain feels like a tetrazzini
It’s no fair you big meanie
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor
A bitch constrictor
I’m gettin’ swallowed by
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a
A bitch constrictor
I’m gettin’ swallowed by a bitch constrictor