♪
(footsteps)
(trips)
(laughs)
(knife whips)
Ah!
I'm going to kill you!
You twisted fucking bitches!
Fucking cunts!
(knife slices)
♪
- So what do you like to be called?
What?
- You girls never have a real name.
What should I call you?
Selena gets all the brown boys.
Kathy gets all the repressed white boys.
They like to call me Kitty Cat.
But my favorite?
Kiwi.
That one, everybody likes.
Kiwi?
Yeah.
Sweet and furry.
Come on, don't you have a sense of humor?
You're not funny.
Well then, let's just fuck and forget the small talk.
I asked for classy and I got a gutter whore?
Take it or leave it, baby.
This is the best there is.
(pistol-whip)
I think I will take it.
Is that all you've got?
(bites)
(punches)
(headbutt)
Trash needs to be taken out.
(gun shot)
(spits)
All you had to do was open your legs.
Do you have any idea how much trouble you're causing me?
How much money I'm losing because of you?
Look at my face. Do you think I give a fuck?
I don't care if he wanted to rip your face clean off.
This guy was big time.
And when big time people come to your town
you give them the best you have to offer.
You give them the best liquor.
You give them the best cocaine.
You give them the best pussy.
If they smack you around a little bit
you take that shit with a smile.
Is that what you would do?
Fuck no.
I don't take shit from anybody.
But I'm me, and you're you.
And you take that shit.
You know what you don't do?
You don't shoot the man worth a fucking million dollars to me.
And call me and expect me to clean up the fucking mess
and expect me to be full of shits and giggles.
Now what do you plan on doing about it?
Well listen up, honey.
You better come up with something real brilliant to save your cunt ass.
- Ladies and gentlemen!
Get your boners ready for...
Fageeda Cunt!
♪
What the mother fuck? Bella Goddamn Muerte
Yeah, good to see you too
What the fuck are you doing here? I told you I don't want to see you again.
I'm done with your bullshit so you need to take your little ass and go on home.
I'm done.
Look, I fucked up real bad.
I've got no one else to turn to and I've got nowhere else to go.
Mm-hmm
They don't just want me dead. They want me hurt.
And I'm afraid it's going to be Lexi.
What the fuck are you talkin' about?
They're gonna kill Lexi. My little sister.
Who?
♪
(footsteps)
(Russian accent) What we are doing here?
Tools. I need my tools.
What, we are going to tune up car?
Just trust me, alright?
Trust you? Last time I trust you was in Thailand...
The hooker remember?
(laughs) Yeah
That was man!
(laughter)
Why you set me up with man?
That was just funny
You've always been crazy, I notice every day
- You guys ever been to a psychic?
Say what?!
What the hell did you go to psychic for?
To get secret magical love connection.
Nah, nah. She just..
I just went--- I wanted---
You want your future? Ok.
I see..
I see!
A beautiful, busty, buxom babe
Just delicious
With a big, fat, red cock.
(mimics gunshot)
Ha ha!
I just--- it didn't feel right, you know?
She said something about Mars was out of retro--- retro-grad
Retrograde!
I talk English gooder than you.
Yeah? I wouldn't be proud of that.
Fucking Rooskie.
What'd she tell you? Some fat hooker was going to suck you off?
Ho ho!
She said just to avoid anything physical.
Nothing violent, man.
I don't know. It just kind of got to me,
You trying to back the fuck out?
- Grow a pair.
Children!
Get back to work.
- психический
Magical love connection!
Boys, have at.
♪
What the fuck is this?
Why we steal a car with this shit?
Here, you do.
- Blow me, motherfucker.
Hey, you blow me.
(blows into Interlock)
Is a fucking didgeridoo or what?
(beeping)
- You're good at that.
He's had practice,
It's not working.
- You got to give it a minute.
It'll get there.
(beeping)
What the hell? You have experience with this stuff?
- I have experience with blowing.
I understand. That's why I hire you.
My goodness.
что
You have problem back there?
Nah, nah. I'm just hungry.
что?
Hungry?
- Yeah. Food. You got that in your fucking country?
- Your stomach is too big to be empty.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
Fuck you.
C'mon, man. Just pull over somewhere and get a burger or something.
I got low blood sugar, man.
Pull over.
I'm not pulling over!
- C'mon, man. There's a Jack in the Crack right over there.
I am not doing the crack!
Wait, wait, wait.
How about we fuck the burgers and get some fucking tacos?
(flicks tongue)
That's what I'm talking about.
You are what you eat, man.
- Pound it.
This isn't Soviet fucking Russia, man.
Car not drive you.
- That not make any fucking sense!
- What are you talking about?
- You know nothing about Soviet Russia.
I'm just hungry, man.
I need something with some sauce.
You know, special sauce.
- I got your special sauce right here, biyeech.
It's beyotch.
Shut the fuck up.
соси хуй
I'm hungry.
See, we should have gone for some fucking tacos.
That's what you get.
I got your tacos right here, biyeech.
- It's BEYOTCH! -
♪
Guys. Covert,
- Nice going, Jackass.
Thanks.
Nice place.
There's no one fucking here.
Mm. Apples good this time year.
Ah!
- Are you sure we're in the right place?
There's no one fucking here.
Stupid Ruskie son of a bitch.
I can't read this American bullshit.
We're supposed to be Northeast.
This is Southeast.
- Yeah, good one.
- Excellent.
Well, you have your stupid writing
I read Cyrillic
You use the inches
And what is with soccer?
It's called football, not soccer!
You American---
- Call it football again
You think that scares me?
- Call soccer football again!
Football!
It's soccer, asshole!
Children!
Change your diapers. We're getting the right address.
We should use the GPS.
- I can't understand that woman.
(knife clicks)
Nice.
♪
(apple crunches)
(tense music)
(tires squeal)
- Hey!
What do you want?
- Just want to talk.
(bat hits)
Ah!
(chain falls)
что!
Southeast and we wouldn't have to be doing this outside!
You're blaming me now, huh?
And nobody blame "Burger Boy" anyway
What is this Southeast, Northeast quadrants?
What are they for anyway?
And where were you?!
Are you guys fucking done yet?
Let's go, c'mon!
Dont--- fucking burger! I'm going to beat your ass with this bat
You fucking try it.
Let's just get out of here before anyone sees us.
This is bullshit.
(solemn music plays)
(sobbing)
Lexxi!
These fuckers are dead!
Hi Mr. Ramirez!
That's the bad one.
Oh, I'm so sorry
Don't worry, Dearie
First impressions don't mean shitting bit of difference to me
Bathroom is back there
Bedroom is beside it
Kitchen is over here
Dishes go up here
Cups up there
I got some spices in that cabinet
Oh, and the dishwasher works just fine
I got handlebars on the toilet
You're lucky you won't have to wipe my ass
Oh, Mr. Ramirez, it's no big deal
It's all part of the job
I can also get in and out of the tub by myself
But you'll have to give me a spongebath
Like I said, Mr. Ramirez
It's part of my job. It's nothing I haven't seen before
It ain't all that bad
You get to sneak a peek sometimes, anyway
- Sometimes I get nightmares
And it kickstarts my pain
- I'm going to kick and punch
And I might even cry
When that happens, you're going to have to wake me
And get me to take my pills
Don't worry, Mr. Ramirez, I'm trained for this kind of thing
I'm going to take good care of you
Hmm, well...
Sometimes you're going to have to calm me down
- I've got some really good drugs for that
That's all good and well, but that isn't exactly what I had in mind
(smacks ass)
Mr. Ramirez! You're a bad man
I can be a good man
Not everything's broke, you know
Look, Mr. Ramirez, let's just keep this professional, Ok?
You and I both know why they sent you to this job
What, I need to earn my keep?
It's none of your business
Let's get this straight
I'm your nurse, not your whore.
What's this then?
You were a prison bitch, now you're my bitch
That's none of your business!
You need to be on your best behavior or else.
Just one call about mistreating this old man, and you're out of a job, Honey.
Won't that revoke your parole?
(door knocks)
Are you expecting someone?
What?
I know I shouldn't be bothering you at work
- What the fuck?
Those fuckers got Lexxi!
(door slams)
You know what? Fuck it.
(whips)
You call whoever the fuck you want
You call, and you tell them I'm the biggest, baddest, bitch you've ever seen!
I know you're trying to go straight, but we need you
Just tell me who the fuck I need to kill
(electronic music)
(footsteps)
We need to talk
Girl, it is all fucked up
Lexxi's dead
Well say something!
Look
It's been a rough day
That last performance really took a lot out of her
Obviously, you girls need to talk
But could you at least give us a minute to get cleaned up
And then you can get to business?
Wow.
What the fuck?
Can I get one of those?
It's ok.
Go ahead and get cleaned up, dear
I'll be there in a minute
What do you want from me?
Alright, ladies, I'm going to show you how this is done
(phone dials, rings)
Yeah, hi
Yeah, my order is broken
I'm not really happy with it
I'm going to need someone to take care of it for me
Yeah, could you have your representative meet me outside?
Let's say 20 minutes?
Yeah, I know where that is
I can do that
Perfect
Thank you
In just a minute, he's going to walk out
He knows I'm a tired housewife, and I want my husband dead
That way I can collect the insurance money and freely bang my friend in a band
So it's just like that?
Ordering a fucking pizza?
Sure is
Apparently this is a pretty healthy business
Sad thing is I wouldn't know half this shit had I not gotten locked up
My girls in the clink showed me some fucked up shit
Goddamn
Look. Quickest service in town
Let's get this fucker, ladies
Hi
How you doin'?
I don't know, I've never done anything like this before
Of course you haven't
Are you the only guy that does this?
Are you a fucking cop?
What? No!
I'm the guy you come to around here.
You're the guy that knows people?
(laughs) Yeah, something like that
What am I doing here? What do you need?
Well, it's my husband
I got you
Alright, well first I'm going to need some shit from you
I'm going to need 500
Dollars?
(laughs)
Add another 3 zeros to that, and we're set
What else do you need?
I'm going to need pictures, addresses, phone numbers
what he does, where he goes
Is it wrong that this turns me on?
Yeah, it's wrong. Are you a bad girl?
Wanna go somewhere?
Let's go.
What the fuck?
What's the problem?
You ever seen this girl, motherfucker?
Oh fuck!
(knife slashes)
What do you think the odds are this kind of thing happening to anyone else?
Nothing surprises me.
Of course these assholes would be coming into my club practically every night
before they end up killing one of the only bitches I've ever loved
I've been shoving my pussy in their faces for who knows how long
Am I shocked?
Do I look bothered?
I'm tell ya. It's a small town.
Are you ready for this shit?
Can't be much different than the other thing I do
It's not half as classy, that's for damn sure
You know you're never going to be able to show your face around here again, right?
Can I tell you how much that breaks my fucking heart?
Let's go kill a bitch.
♪
I can't believe they won't let me change my rubles.
They don't take rubles here!
What makes you think they would take rubles?
America. America.
You did not tell me to take them
Can you believe this guy?
I don't get this shit
Seriously, I don't get it.
- To Rob -
для вашего здоровья
You have my sympathies, friend
Does anybody understand this shit?
What the hell happened?
- What's there to understand?
He should have been better at crossing rivers by now
- Fuck you.
- Rob's dead
Mom is going to be pissed
Who does that anyway?
Who kills a guy and leaves him to bleed out in middle of the fucking Rio Grande?
I mean what kind of fucking world is this?
It could have been mafia, banditos, muscular sclerosis
Who knows? It could have been anybody
What the fuck are you staring at?!
So, which one of you pretty motherfuckers wants a dance?
- He does -
- Come on, motherfucker. Your ass is mine
- You're assholes
Have fun!
Better him than us
♪
What's the matter? Don't you like girls?
Fuck yeah, I do
The only problem is my brother
He was left for dead
Is there anything I can do to cheer you up?
Maybe
What happened?
Some crazy bitches
Hmm, bitches
What are you going to do about it?
I'm going to find them
Grab them
(moaning)
Hold them down while I cut them
from groin to neck
And then what are you going to do?
I'll tell you what I'm going to do
I'm going to play with their insides, you know?
You gonna cut them with that big-ass knife?
Hell yeah
You like cutting people, don't you?
(laughs) Yeah
You like cutting little girls, too
What did you say?
(laughs)
Ah!
Ow! No, no no
(neck cracks)
Cut that, you bitch
(straps snap)
What the fuck is he doing, taking nap in there or what?
Hell if I know. He's probably enjoying himself
You go check. I do not need his birthday party suit in my head
How come I have to go check?
You go check!
Why?
Because you're American. You know him better
Go check now. сейчас
Go check
♪
Hey!
Let's go!
Hey
Let's go
I know what you're doing in there. Finish up
If you don't hurry up, I'm going to get pictures
pictures and---
(stutters)
Your mom is going to see them on your Facebook!
Hurry up!
I show you my tats I get in the zone
The Gulag
I get these for each year
I -- I in Gulag
Uh, these here for each head I take
This mean-- the cross mean that I get shot
And let's see here
This mean I prepared for anything
And here, I follow thieves code
This one in here: I make best Schezuan Chicken in the world
This here, I get convicted by soviet court
On the knees here
mean I kneel to no one
to no authority
(muffled scream)
What happened?
Who did this?
(stammers)
Calm down
We've got to get out of here!
Someone is hunting our friends down
Calm down!
Ow!
Who is the cocoa whore that did this?
(screams)
Who did this?!
I don't know!
You tell me now!
It's my first day!
You tell me now or I kill you!
Tell me!
Fageeda Cunt!
What the fuck kind of name is Fageeda Cunt?!
I don't know!
It doesn't matter, ok?
We need to get out of here. Go!
Fuck
(sobbing)
(gun cocks)
So, how do we find stripper whore anyway?
¿yo qué sé?
It's not like they're in the phonebook
What do you want to do, go back to the strip club?
- Too dangerous
Excuse me, sir, my fellows and I were at your establishment recently
and we believe one of your employees may have killed our friend
Can you help us out?
(scoffs) I'd be happy to
Besides, it's too dangerous
I owe Candy 50 dollars still
Good job
She's good looking
I bet she is
Inches? Who the hell uses inches?
(phone rings)
Hey, it's me
Who are you calling, your mother?
Is she stripper whore too?
Come on, think about it
- I am thinking about your mother
Suck it
No, we've got a bit of a problem with that last job
No, like a really big fucking problem
What kind of bullet is this? It should be---
Shut up. I'm trying to talk
Keep trying
No, like a really big fucking problem
Like 2 of my friends dead kind of problem!
Look, just ---
Do you ---
Shut up. Let me ask.
Do you know a stripper by the name Fageeda Cunt?
♪
Are you sure this right address?
I don't read upside down like you, motherfucker
What are you, Bruce Lee?
This isn't The Green Hornet
Bust that open
Why don't I ring the doorbell? They open up for us
Dude, we're not selling Girl Scout cookies to them
You have Girl Scout cookies?
I wish
The window is open. Get in.
I'm not getting in there
I'm 188 centimeters. You're what, 122? 124?
I'm 170 centimeters, ok?
I've got your 170 centimeters right here
You know many sharp things I carry on me, right?
The only sharp thing you have is your penis, definitely not your brain
Now get in.
I'm not going to. No!
And don't forget to unlock for me!
I'm going to kick your ass
I can't beleive I'm doing this shit again
I thought I was going straight
Like we twisted your fucking arm, bitch
Shut up
I don't know how you all did it
I could never leave
It wasn't that hard, girl
It's not like you went very far.
What was that, bitch?
Look, you're a stripper.
That's not walking away from community pussy. That's not even a vacation
You want to know what the difference is?
I use what I got
I play these ugly, horny-ass men
Make them think that I'm in love with them
They give me money. They buy me nice things
Only difference is, I don't have to fuck them
Or I don't get my ass beat because one of them is in bad mood or some shit
Or worse, like they did to Lexxi
(muffled noises)
Did you hear that?
What? They had other door
It was unlocked
Fuck you
You don't read American bullshit, remember?
(scoffs)
Don't start tweeking, chica
I gotta ask you something
What was up with that fucked up shit you were doing?
It's like you said
We give people what they want
They want pain. They want sex. They want violence
I give people what they crave
But you had paint covered on some naked dude
It's the same rhythm and motion
I'd rather put on a show than take part in the madness of reality
If it wasn't for Lexxi, I'd tell you all to go fuck yourseves
What the fuck? (laughs)
No, no. She's right
I got locked up for this shit
You guys think it's hard out here?
Man, try being caged in fighting off worse bitches than we are day to day
I'm serious
Man, I swore I would rather die than go back to that
And then look
The first fucking pervert gets his hands on someone
And I'm right back fucking in this shit
For Lexxi, right?
(Fageeda laughs)
Something funny, bitch?
She has a man-pet, and you?
You talk too damn much (laughs)
Fuck you, hooker!
Fuck you!
(screaming)
(paper falls)
Hold this.
Looky looky, the Commie and Mick. Can't catch me, I'm the Gingerbread Bitch!
Fuck!
What the fuck is a Gingerbread Bitch?
One of those fucking---
Hey look, they have apples!
I've got to go blow off some steam
(screaming)
God damn, I fucking missed you bitches
So, who's next?
Hey, cutie
You here for a lesson?
I'm gonna teach you one
It's a shame I gotta kill you
You're kind of cute
Sorry lady, I don't date psychos
You killed the wrong bitch, Bruce Lee
It doesn't matter what happens here
You're already dead
I get it, revenge
You think you're tough?
Ah!
(spits)
I'll show you tough
Something's wrong
Fuck that. She can take care of herself
I don't know. Maybe we shouldn't have left her by herself
(doorbell)
♪ ominous music
(retching, sobbing)
No! No!
No!
(sobbing)
Oh my god!
So, recipe-- You take this to your grave
I tell nobody this
So you hold on, not tell anybody until your dying day
Even on your dying day, you tell no one
Good?
Sure.
Good. So you get the fish oil
because the fatty omega acids are important for health
use all organic materials
The ingredients must be fresh, organic
Organ-tick?
- Organic.
Organic. And you want to have the onions---
(low crashing sound)
White onions and the green onions are very important, and---
Get ready to die you motherf---
(gunshot)
So you want the green onions, very important
Make sure you get---
Oh, I'm sorry. I get more ammo.
I get more ammo?
I get more eh, fresh chicken
Take care of that bitch for me, ok?
You got it
You're coming with me
♪ Eerie music
Well babe, I hope you're better than your friend here
Oh please, let's not ruin this with you talking
Fair enough
♪ high powered music
(punch)
Ughn!
(exhales loudly)
Ah!
Ha! Ughn!
Ugh!
(writhing)
Where are they?!
Fuck you, whore!
Ungh, Gah!!
Where are they!
Fuck you, I'm not telling you any shit
Ah!
Where.. are they?
Fuck you! You can go to hell!
(tweaking wounds)
Ah! Ah!!
I can do this all night
Alright!
(choking)
I'll tell you!
(exhales)
♪
(engine revs)
(sniffs)
Ah, the cheap shit
(tazer zaps)
(gunshots)
Bet you wish you'd stayed in the Motherland, Mutherfucker.
Nyet, I love it here
(choking, gurgling)
Wait. If I survive, I cook you Schezuan Chicken
♪
(spits)
Hey, look who showed up
Now, now. That's not necessary
(snaps)
Besides, I don't know how many bullets you fired out there, but it sounded like a lot
(knives unsheathe)
Seriously, we don't have to do all this
Besides, I kind of like you crazy bitches
Well, except for this one here
By the way, did she tell you why she got you all into this whole mess?
Yeah, because you sent your dogs after Lexxi
(laughs) That's cute
Dogs
Obedient, loyal
You say "sick them," and they attack
You didn't even question it, did you?
I mean you ladies really fucked up my guys
Thing is, I told this fucking bitch to make up for her mistake
And she did
Seemed like a dick move to me, but what the hell
A lot of people can throw their own family under the bus
God, and I know this bitch too
I knew I should have killed the right fucking whore
(snaps)
Because I'm short four fucking hit-men
Do you know how hard it is to find four good fucking hit-men in this town?
Of course, you seem pretty talented
And one hit-lady almost makes up for it
So what do you say?
I want to hear it from her
What the fuck are you thinking? Kill this bitch!
What are you thinking? They killed Lexxi!
It's fucked up
You're just going to let her kill me?
What kind of bitch do you think I am?
You're just going to walk away? Don't turn your back on me!
Lexxi, Fageeda, Harley. They're all dead, and it's because of you?
It could be just us now
Just you and me
Hey, you think about that job
(gunshot)
♪
(singing "Mahna Mahna")
(laughing)
(laughs)
What? Who?
Who?
-Say it again
(mocking owl)
(laughs)
Fuck you, hooker!
Oh, bitch!
(laughing)
Ow! Ow!
(laughs)
You pulled my hair!
Don't touch my damn hair!
You didn't break a nail, girl!
- Ok, I'm rolling
Can I "axe" you a question? (laughs)
(laughing)
Oh no you didn't!